<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AbsoluteLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content"
  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
  xmlns:admobsdk="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/org.armyapp.marinecorps">
    <com.admob.android.ads.AdView android:id="@id/ad" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" admobsdk:backgroundColor="#ff000000" admobsdk:textColor="#ffffffff" admobsdk:keywords="Android application" />
    <TextView android:textSize="16.0sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:id="@id/widget27" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="NCO Creed" android:layout_x="2.0px" android:layout_y="48.0px" />
    <ScrollView android:id="@id/ScrollView01" android:layout_width="480.0px" android:layout_height="175.0px" android:layout_x="2.0px" android:layout_y="60.0px">
        <AbsoluteLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content"
          xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
            <TextView android:id="@id/widget27" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text=" I am the backbone of the United States Marine Corps, I am a Marine Non-Commissioned Officer.  \n\n I serve as part of the vital link between my commander (and all officers) and enlisted Marines.  \n\n I will never forget who I am or what I represent.  \n\n I will challenge myself to the limit and be ever attentive to duty.  \n\n I am now, more than ever, committed to excellence in all that I do, so that I can set the proper example for other Marines.  \n\n I will demand of myself all the energy, knowledge and skills I possess, so that I can instill confidence in those I teach.  \n\n I will constantly strive to perfect my own skills and to become a good leader.  \n\n Above all I will be truthful in all I say or do.  \n\n My integrity shall be impeccable as my appearance.  \n\n I will be honest with myself, with those under my charge and with my superiors.  \n\n I pledge to do my best to incorporate all the leadership traits into my character.  \n\n For such is the heritage I have received from that long, illustrious line of professionals who have worn the bloodstripe so proudly before me.  \n\n I must give the very best I have for my Marines, my Corps and my Country for though today I instruct and supervise in peace, tomorrow, I may lead in war." android:layout_x="0.0px" android:layout_y="22.0px" />
        </AbsoluteLayout>
    </ScrollView>
    <Button android:id="@id/xBackButton" android:layout_width="95.0px" android:layout_height="38.0px" android:text="BACK" android:layout_x="385.0px" android:layout_y="235.0px" />
</AbsoluteLayout>
